var questionArray = [{

    
    question: 'Which Country has the longest coastline in the world?',
    choices:['USA',	'Brazil','Morocco',	'Canada'],
    answer:'Canada',
},
{    
    question: 'Which country holds the worlds largest population?',
    choices: ['India','Iran','China','Mexico',],
    answer: 'China',
},
{  
    question: 'What is the most popular language spoken in Sudan?',
    choices: ['Arabic','Fulani','Swahili','Amharic',],
    answer:'Arabic',
},
{    
    question: 'Which country does the cultural dance Dabke originate from?',
    choices:['Iran',	'Palestine',	'Portugal',	'Nigeria' ],
    answer: 'Palestine',
},
{       
    question: 'After the Nile, what is the longest river in the world?',
    choices:['Amazon',	'Mississippi',	'Yangtze',	'Colombia' ],
    answer:'Amazon',
},
{
    question: 'In which country is it a taboo to write someoneâ€™s name in red?',
    choices:['Turkey',	'South Korea',	'Thailand',	'Chile',],
    answer:'South Korea',
},
{
    question:'In which Chinese ethnic group do brides cry for a month as a wedding preparation?',
    choices:['Fuji', 'Uyghur',	'Tujia', 'Tibetan',],
    answer: 'Fuji',
},
{
    question:'How many languages are spoken in Kenya?',
    choices: ['42',	'30',	'12',	'68',],
    answer: '68',
},
{
    question: 'Which country has a ban on religion?',
    choices: ['Tajikistan',	'Pakistan',	'Iraq',	'South Africa',],
    answer: 'Tajikistan',
},
{
    question:'Which country has a ban on chewing gum?',
    choices: ['Saudi Arabia',	'Haiti',	'Peru',	'Singapore',],
    answer: 'Singapore',
}
];

    


